http://www.forumappliances.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:At Forum Home Appliances we know how important it is to protect your personal information. Whether you are shopping with us online or in person we want to make every customer experience safe and secure. In keeping with that goal, we have developed this Privacy Policy to outline our guidelines for the collection and use of personal information by us.Online Purchases:While using our webstore, you will be asked to voluntarily provide certain personal information (such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, or credit card information). We use this information to complete your transaction. If you choose not to provide requested personal information, you will not be able to engage in transactions through our webstore.We may also use your personal information to contact and correspond with you regarding your online purchase or to respond to your inquiries.In-Store Purchases:When you purchase a product or service from us, you may need to provide us with contact and payment information (such as credit card information) so that we can process your request. Examples where we need contact information include delivery services, product servicing, in-home installations, and warranty coverage.Will you disclose the information you collect?We will not sell your personal information. However we may share your information with third parties acting on our behalf or as permitted or required by law.Disclosure to Service ProvidersWe may share your personal information with certain service providers in order to provide products and services to you, to verify and validate information, and to address customer service matters. Examples of service providers include credit card issuers, product service depots, warranty providers, and delivery services. To reduce the risk of fraud or misuse of personal information, we may also verify your personal information, including but not limited to your address and credit card information, with third party service providers.We will use reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information is used in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If you do not wish us to provide your personal information to those service providers, we may be unable to process your transaction.Legal Disclosure:We may disclose your information as permitted or required to by law; for example:
to a government institution or other person or entity that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information;
where we have reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful in the investigation of unlawful activity;
to comply with a subpoena or warrant or an order made by a court, person or entity with jurisdiction to compel the production of information;
to comply with court rules regarding the production of records and information; and
to our legal counsel.
Customer ServiceToll Free: 1-877-893-8896Monday – Friday 9:30am - 6:00pm PST
